- 考特尼！
- Courtney!
灵 异  空 间
我感觉有人牵着我的手，指引着我...
I had this sensation of someone taking my hand, guiding me...
我抬头看见了光
I looked up and I saw this light.
巨大的光墙，非常亮
The giant wall of light. Brighter...
突然间，我到了另一个地方
All of a sudden, I was in a different place.
纯能量
Pure energy.
难以用语言表达我的经历
I fail to find words that can describe what I experienced.
在那时，我感觉我的灵魂脱离了我身体
At that point, I had that out-of-body experience.
我记得之前那种难受的感觉
I remember a feeling of being sucked backwards,
就像刚被人从水中救出来一样
like being pulled through water.
我的大脑是空白的
I wasn't having thoughts of my own.
大量的答案，信息向我涌来
Answers, uh, messages coming through me.
颜色异常的鲜艳，我从未见过
Colors were so vivid. Colors I've never seen before.
然后我被推回自己身体中
Then I was pushed right back into my body.
我能从上方看见我的身体
I could actually see my body from above,
看着毫无生气
like it was lifeless.
并漂浮着
And I was floating up...
一切我认为重要的东西
Everything I thought was important was
在爱的面前都如此渺小
dwarfed by this sense of love.
我能感觉到拉力
And I could feel this pull,
一种力量把我向黑色的隧道中拖拽
a force trying to drag me down this black tunnel.
要带我去哪？
Where is it taking me?
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what's going on.
我想我疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
我看见一些事
I'm seeing things.
一些我做过的事
Something I did.
对不起
I'm sorry.
九 年 后
你好，劳伦
Hello, Lauren.
你感觉怎么样？
How are you feeling?
你晚上癫痫发作了
You had a seizure tonight.
你现在在三体艾曼纽医学中心
You're at Trinity Emmanuel Medical Center.
劳伦
Lauren,
你知道你的心脏停止过吗？
do you know that your heart stopped?
停止了好几分钟
You were gone for several minutes,
创伤急救小组把你救了回来
but the trauma team brought you back.
你还记得吗？
Do you remember any of that?
有没有感觉到或看到什么？
If you felt anything, if you saw anything?
亲爱的，你是不是失去了亲人？
Did you lose someone, sweetheart?
她在这
She's in here.
我们带你去做个全身扫描 你会好起来的
We're taking you to Imaging.You'll be okay.
一个患者转到第五病房
One for transfer in five.
准备好了吗？一，二，三
Ready? One, two, three.
转自圣十字医院
Transfer from Holy Cross.
38岁建筑工人，从横梁摔了下来
38-year-old construction worker, fell off a beam.
GCS  格拉斯哥昏迷等级
一直昏迷 昏迷等级6
Persistent coma. GCS 6.
-我叫驻院医生来  -嗯
- I'll page the resident. - Mmm-hmm.
已经来了，交给我吧
Already done. I got this.
你们到底谁负责？
Which one of you is in charge here?
是我的班
It's my intake.
事实上，是我一个人值班
Actually, I'm the one on duty.
我来吧 我来吧 谢谢
I got it. I got it. Thank you.
确认6级昏迷进行标准流程
Standard procedure for a GCS 6 admit
准备注射两个大口径的安定
calls for two large-bore IVs and diazepam on standby.
安定药物不会起到好的作用
Seizure meds won't do any good.
出问题的是他的脊柱，不是大脑
Whatever is wrong is in his spinal column, not his brain.
你用的是什么急救方案？
And what medical protocol are you citing?
方案是死的，人是活的
The protocol of actually living in the real world,
蹩脚医疗机构的人诊断不出脊柱损伤
where guys with crappy HMOs go undiagnosed for spinal injuries.
事实上，他用了抗癫痫药物
Actually, he's on seizure meds,
那说明急救方案是对的
which is the medical protocol of reading his chart.
哦不，不不不
Oh, shit. No, no, no.
-该死  -额...
- Shit. -Uh, uh...
怎么了？
What is it?
呼吸衰竭
Respiratory failure.
他可能有大出血
He might be hemorrhaging.
呼叫神经外科医生，并准备好CT
Page Neurosurgery, call a code, and get CT on standby.
学生们，离开病房
Students, clear the room.
嘿，怎么了，发生了什么？
Hey. What is it? What's wrong?
你知道头颅内有
Did you know that there's 12 pairs of nerves
12对神经吗？
just within the cranial area?
额，动眼神经，
The, urn... The oculomotor,
滑车神经，舌咽神经，和...
the trochlear, the glossopharyngeal, and...
其他九个的名字我记不清了
Nine others whose names I cannot remember.
我怎么也记不住那些术语
I cannot absorb any more terminology.
那种感觉就像... 手臂上有疹，睡不着觉一样
I have, like... A rash on my arm. I can't sleep.
你知道吗，我母亲投入了
mother invested
她的一生在我的教育上
life savings into my education.
来
Come on.
别想了，这一晚已经够难受了
Come on, that's enough suffering for one night.
我们出去散散步吧
Let's get out of here. Yeah?
好冷
It's cold.
我们曾经是朋友，对吗？
We used to be friends, right?
-什么... -我们第一年
-What is... -Like, our first year,
听讲课时我们就坐在一起
when we would sit together at lecture.
-还记得吗？- 嗯
- Remember? -Mmm.
我们还经常一起跑去买咖啡
And we'd, like, go running and get coffee.
一起玩耍
Hang out. Do stuff.
我们还是朋友啊
We're still friends, though.
不，我们现在基本不讲话
No, we don't talk.
只是工作和..竞争
We just work and... And compete.
谁能最快诊断出贝尔式麻痹？
Who's the fastest to make a diagnosis of Bell's palsy?
快，氯羟去甲安定有哪七种副作用？
Quick, what's the seven side effects of Ativan?
你懂得，上个周，我第二学期彻底挂了
You know, just last week, a second-year committed suicide.
我不像你，考特尼，你一定会是个好医生
God, Court, you're gonna be such a good doctor.
医学，对你来说太简单了
Medicine just, like, comes easy to you.
我想到一个让我们有更多时间在一起的方法
You know, I think there's a way that we could spend more time together.
-你什么意思？ -恩，我在想
- What do you mean? -Well, I'm just wondering
如果你稍稍帮助我
if you'd help me on this little, like,
关于我课外研究的项目
extracurricular project I've been working on.
额... 我们只是
Uh... We just...
我们关于神经层的考试只有不到十天了
We have neuro shelf exams in, like, 10 days.
我觉得我不会过
I don't really feel like I'm gonna make it.
哦，一旦解剖完成 美好的假期如天堂一般
Oh, Once One Takes The Anatomy Final, Very Good Vacations Are Heavenly.
-什么？ -一种帮助记忆的短语
- What? -it's a mnemonic phrase.
你用它来记住12对颅内神经
You use it to remember the 12 cranial nerves.
-是啊 -哇，谢谢
- Yeah. -Ah. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
不过，我仍然很希望你能来帮忙
But, yeah, I'm...I really would love your help.
看看吧
Maybe.
嘿
Hey.
那是什么？
What's in those?
一瓶是激浪加阿德拉
First one's Mountain Dew laced with Adderall.
Adderall的主要作用成分为苯丙胺 可以提高注意力，增加体力消耗，同时抑制食欲。
另一瓶是解酒的浓咖啡
Other's a chaser of espressos.
-加在一起就能让心脏高速运转 -嘿，杰米
- Together, it's a liquid heart attack. -Hey, Jamie.
哦，我的天
Oh, Jesus.
嘿
Hey
“嘿，杰米”昨晚你在哪？
"Hey, Jamie." Where were you last night?
你看起来还是很兴奋
Your eyes are still dilated.
一位25岁女性，昨晚发病
25-year-old female, admitted last night.
身体左半边麻木，并伴恶心呕吐
Complaining of numbness on left side, nausea, vomiting.
对她体检有什么需要注意的吗？
Anything of note from the physical exam?
左右眼看到的
Sees the color red differently
红色不一样，有口腔溃疡
between left and right eye, and oral ulcers.
索菲亚，我们应该进行什么检查？
Sophia, what test should we run?
腰椎穿刺，然后做脑部磁共振成像
A lumbar puncture, then MRI of the brain.
错，顺序不对，先做成像后进行手术
Fine, but reverse the order. Images first, then procedure.
初步诊断是什么，布拉德
Preliminary diagnosis, Brad.
-垂体囊肿？-不对
- Pituitary cyst? -No.
杰米
Jamie.
额...
Uh...
杰克
Jackie.
-额，中风？-我的天
- Um, stroke? -My God.
你需要更加努力
You need to do better than this.
你们全部人
All of you.
你们知道现在社会上最大年龄群体的人是多少岁吗？
What do you think the largest age demographic is in our society today?
你们这个年龄
You.
20岁 年轻的成年人，意味着
Young adults in their 20s, which means
至少有1000人在等着
that there are at least 1,000 people waiting
顶替你们的位置
to take your spot.
我们不是做医生培训的乡村俱乐部
And we are not in the business of training country club doctors,
也不会在连基本功课都不做
nor do we waste our time on students who think
的学生身上浪费时间
that they can skate by doing the least work necessary.
我们教的是能突破自己的学生
We are here to educate students who push themselves,
那些有能力做出新发现的
those who are capable of making new discoveries
和可以推进人类知识的人
and actually move the dial on human knowledge.
那些不思进取的人
And for those of you who think that's too much,
这不是你呆的地方
then you should leave.
现在你就可以走
And by that, I mean now.
玛洛,我问你一个问题
Marlo, if I were to tell you
如果患者的家庭背景是地中海
that the patient's family background was Mediterranean,
或是希腊土耳其，最有可能患什么病？
i.e., Greek or Turkish, what would the diagnosis be?
我不认为那会在你的笔记中找到
I don't think you'll find it in your notebook.
是白塞氏病
It's Behcet's disease.
谢谢你，雷
Thank you, Ray.
下一个
Moving on.
-你为什么会在这种活动打工？
- Why are you working this event?
你根本不缺钱 你睡在游艇上
You're a trust-fund kid. You sleep on a sailboat.
是啊，但这里有个非常火辣的酒席承办人
Yeah, but there's this really hot caterer
-我准备和她约会 -啊
- I've been trying to meet. -Ah.
看看这些古板的老医生和他们的白葡萄酒
Look at all these stodgy old docs with their white wine
还有高尔夫
and their golf games.
我认为那种生活还不赖
I don't think it's such a bad life.
我不知道你
I don't know about you,
我是不会在接下来的40年中一直做前列腺检查
but I'm certainly not gonna spend the next 40 years doing prostate exams.
没人在努力工作了
No one pays their dues anymore.
我们这一代的人都想当企业家
Our generation,it's all about entrepreneurship.
是吗，那你要去干什么？
Yeah, so what are you gonna do?
我要去洛杉矶
I'm going to LA.
看我的帅脸
Look at this face.
我要成为医学界的安德森·库珀
I'm gonna be the Anderson Cooper of celebrity medicine.
安德森·库珀，是美国出色的记者，作家以及电视名人
好吧
Okay.
“嗨 妈妈 我下午在这里”
"Oh, hi, Mom. It's my afternoon check-in."
这一点不好笑
That's funny. Cool. Okay.
你知道我现在拿她没办法
You know there's nothing I can do about her right now.
她真的为了监督你而搬到了这里？
Did she really move here just to keep tabs on you?
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
嘿，别拍了，看
Hey, come on, look.
-我的都倒满了-好的
- My station is full. -Okay.
你太慢了
You're so behind.
好的，先生我来给你做个睾丸检查
Okay, sir, got to give you a testicular exam.
-很快就好 -什么？不
- Should just take a minute. -What? No.
-不好意思了 -等...等一下
- Excuse the reach. -Wait a... Wait a minute!
我也不想
I don't enjoy it either.
闭上眼想象我是一个穿条纹衣服的小护士
Just close your eyes and pretend I'm the candy-stripe girl.
什么？放开我
What? Get... Get the hell off of me!
等一下
Hold on.
- 条纹衣服的小护士 -啊喔！放开
- Candy-stripe girl. -Whoa, whoa! Get...
-不，等一下 - 停下！你在干什么？
- No, wait a minute. -Stop! What are you doing?
他不需要睾丸检查
He doesn't need a testicular exam.
他不需要？
He doesn't?
在靠近我，我就揍死你
Come near me again, I'm killing you.
不好意思，我想我搞混了
You know, I think I got mixed up.
上面说的是这位住院病人想做
It says here the resident wanted
一个神经检查，不是睾丸检查
a neural test for that guy, not a testicular exam.
我不敢想象我告诉你了一个错误的信息
I can't imagine how I passed the wrong information to you.
“非常搞笑”
Very funny.
雷有时真混蛋，你们知道吗？
Ray can be a real dick sometimes. You guys notice that?
我认为他很有魅力
I think he's intriguing.
动起来，学生们 今天没有午休
Let's go, people. No lunch break today.
每个部门的床位都满了，我们必须在急诊室等待转移
Every bed in the unit is full, and we got referrals waiting in the ER.
下午就开始检查病房
Get moving on afternoon rounds.
借过
Excuse me.
你今天晚上有安排吗？
Do you have plans tonight?
第一年酒会狂欢
First-years are having a wingding.
宿舍调酒 放DJ,但是我不在其中
Dorm punch and a deejay, but I'm not above it.
我已经等不及体验那种天旋地转的感觉
I can't wait for the anesthesia rotation.
那些家伙能拿到最棒的药品
Those guys have access to the best drugs.
在找这个吗？
Looking for this?
对啊
Hell yeah.
我在我床边的桌子上找到的
I found it on my nightstand.
待会见
See you later.
第二年我毫无经验
These second-years have no tact,
就这样出现在我的同事面前
coming up to me like that in front of my colleague.
是的，我们是同事，不是吗？
Yeah, we're colleagues, aren't we?
是的，我们一起愉快的玩耍
I mean, we have fun together.
恩，差不多
Yeah, kinda.
晚点想和我一起搞点好玩的吗？
Do you want to have fun with me later?
考特尼·霍姆斯，我有些惊讶
Courtney Holmes, I am mildly surprised
和你进行这段谈话
to be having this conversation with you.
但提议我接受
But offer accepted.
午夜，地下室，C层
Midnight, basement, sub level C.
你想和我在地下室见面？
You want to meet me in the basement?
C层，在老建筑下面
Sublevel C, underneath the old building.
坐货梯来
And take the service elevator,
因为没有摄像监控
'cause it doesn't have surveillance cameras.
是，好主意
Yeah. Good idea.
不
No.
我的天
Jesus!
- 你迟到了
- You're late.
我们在下面做什么？
What are we doing down here?
快，我们没有那么多时间
Come on, we don't have much time.
好吧，考特尼我们要做什么？
Okay, Courtney, what's going on?
过了午夜了，我现在应该在学习
It's past midnight.I should be studying.
我们马上就好，好吗？
We're almost there, okay?
这都是什么？
What is all of this?
他们五年前就在这了
They put this in five years ago.
以防自然灾害而断电
In case of a natural disaster, loss of power.
医疗设备齐全，而且还没使用过
It's a fully functioning hospital,and it never gets used.
哇哦
Whoa.
额，考特尼你到底想干嘛？
Urn, Court, what exactly are you up to?
-额 -哇
- Um... -Wow.
你们两个
Two of you.
杰米，你来什么？
Jamie, what are you doing here?
额，她也没告诉我你在这好吗？
Uh, she didn't tell me about you either, okay?
但是，三个人我也不介意
But, I'm open to a three-way.
恶心，闭嘴
Ew. Shut up.
怎么了？
What?
噢，我喜欢！
Oh, I like it!
扫描仪，摄像机，哪都可以作为我们的床
Scanners, cameras, our choice of beds.
-我们叫多大声都可以 -考特尼，到底来这干什么？
- We can be as loud as we want. -Courtney, what's going on?
我也叫他来帮忙，但他可能想歪了
I asked for his help, too. He probably misinterpreted.
哦，哦 你的意思是我们不玩了吗？
Oh. Oh, you mean we're not getting it on?
等等，你在说什么？
Wait, what are you talking about?
我在寻找大脑哪个区域
I've been searching for the region of the brain
会对濒死的经历进行处理
that is responsible for near-death experiences.
这些是医院里
And these are postmortem scans
给死去的病人的尸体扫描的仪器
of patients that have died in this hospital.
你们是不是忘了什么事
ls there any circumstance under which
-你还没和我爱爱呢？-我的天，别说了
-you'd have sex with me? -God, stop.
看，如果说大脑只是个普通的器官
Look, if the brain is just another organ,
人在死亡的瞬间
why doesn't it just go dark and... And shut off
大脑为什么不停止活动？
at the moment of death?
为什么会有漂浮感？
You know, why the floating?
为什么会看见白光？
Why the white light?
为什么会感觉很平静？
Why the sense of well-being?
我的意思是，为什么会有这些感受？
I mean, what is that experience?
是化学反应，还是别的什么东西？
Is it chemical, or is it something else?
我们为什么不像记录癫痫那样记录这个过程？
Can we map that process the way we map a seizure?
如果我们真能记录下我们死后发生了什么？
What if we could actually document what happens to us after we die?
你想干嘛？
What do you mean?
什么也不会发生，我们会死
Nothing happens. We're dead.
如果我们可以用别的方法证明呢？
What if we could prove otherwise?
你能想象我们会得到多大的实习资金吗？
Can you imagine the residency offers you would get?
别提Oz博士
And forget about Dr. Oz.
我是说，你会成为世界第一研究来世的专家
I mean, you would be the world's first specialist in the afterlife.
好的，你引起了我的注意
Okay, you got my attention.
得了吧，这不是科学
Oh, come on. This isn't science.
-这是伪科学
-This is pseudoscience.
也许是，也许不是
Well, maybe. Maybe not.
只有一种方法可以证明就是我们自己试试
But the only way to find out is to see for ourselves.
所以我想你们俩帮我把心脏停下
So I would like you both to stop my heart.
听着，我大脑活动会在图像扫描仪上
Look, I'll be in the imaging scanner.
那会实时记录下我大脑血流动力的活动
It will take real-time pictures of my brain's hemodynamic activity.
-额 -给我一分钟
- Um... -You give it one minute,
然后把我救回来
and then you bring me back.
等下，你是认真的吗？
Wait, you're serious?
-停止你的心脏？-这是镇静剂
- Stop your heart? -This is propofol.
50毫克会让我睡着
Fifty milligrams will knock me out.
我会裹在冷却的毯子里
I'll be wrapped in a cooling blanket,
把我的核心体温降低至30摄氏度
bringing my core body temperature down to 86 degrees.
一旦成功
And once that happens,
你就给我用除颤器电击我的心脏让我心跳停止
you administer a defibrillator shock to stop my heart.
等一下
Wait a sec.
我签了免责协议，在我包里
Look, I've signed a release. It's in my bag.
它会免除你们的所有责任
It absolves you both of any responsibility.
考特尼，听听你自己说的话
Courtney, think about what you're saying right now.
嘿，听着，如果她疯的以至于愿意尝试，我们怎么能阻止她？
Hey. Look, if she's insane enough to try it, who are we to stop her?
-额 -我还年轻，没关系的
- Um... - Look. I'm young, okay?
我非常健康
I'm in excellent health.
而且你们都受过专业的急救训练
You're both trained in emergency medicine.
-把我救醒应该
- So reviving me should be
-非常简单
-very straightforward.
已经12点18分了
Look, it's 12:18 now.
我看了安保的巡逻时间表
I've checked the schedules for security down here
和清洁工人的
and cleaning crews.
我们还有45分钟了，我们应该快点开始了
We have about 45 minutes, so we should probably get going.
这太疯狂了，不要把我拉进来
What? This is crazy. No, count me out of this.
我不会帮助你来谋杀自己
I am not helping you kill yourself.
那你就呆在门口待命，确保没人进来
Well, then you can stand by the door and make sure nobody comes in.
好，记住，扫描仪里面有磁铁
Okay, remember, there's a magnet in the scanner,
所以不能有药匙或金属出现在这里
so no keys or metal in the room.
听着，我们会成功的
Look, we've got it.
等等，杰米，万一你没把她就回来呢？
Wait, Jamie, what if you can't bring her back?
那我们就把尸体埋掉，制造不在场证据
Then we burn her body, work out our alibi,
然后假装什么也没发生
and pretend like nothing happened.
确保扫描仪正在记录
And make sure that the scanner's recording,
如果没有的话，那这次实验会白白浪费
because if not, then this whole exercise is pointless.
我们可以开始了
We're good to go.
给我重复一下复苏手术流程
Repeat back to me the resuscitation procedure.
只要你一“死”，我就跑向扫描仪
Uh, as soon as you're dead, I'll run the scanner.
到了60秒，我就开始救你
At 60 seconds, I'll start pulling you out
替换热的毛毯
by switching to the heating blanket.
当你的核心体温到达33度，我就开始心脏复苏
When your core temp's back up to 93 degrees, I'll start CPR.
带有肾上腺素和除颤器的急救车待命中
Crash cart is standing by with the epi and the defib.
等等...脑损伤，你会脑损伤的
Wai... Hello? Brain damage. You'll get brain damage.
如果你没有及时复苏我
Not if you resuscitate me in time.
脑细胞可以在没有氧气的情况下存活4分钟
Brain cells can survive without oxygen for at least four minutes.
好吧
Okay.
现在说这是个玩笑还不晚
Now is the point where you say it's all a joke.
好的，给我盖上毯子
Okay, put the blanket on me.
杰米，看看她，她吓坏了
Jamie, look at her. Come on, she's terrified.
这是我身体自然的本能反应
It's just my body's natural survival instincts.
我已经想到了，我试着去克制他
I anticipated this. I'm trying to block it out.
好的
Okay.
现在我要把你杀掉
And now I kill you.
别这样，你们俩会被除名 进监狱的
Come on, you'll both get expelled. You'll go to prison.
如果你不瞎说的话
Only if you blab about it.
好的 我们真的在做这件事
Okay. We're really doing this.
额
Uh...
额，待会见
Uh, see you later.
她晕过去了
She's out.
体温正在下降
Uh, body temp's dropping.
杰米，现在停下吧，好吗？
Okay, look, Jamie, we can stop right here, okay?
她睡着了，然后醒来
She sleeps it off, wakes up,
然后我们假装按照流程走了一遍
and we just pretend that we followed through with it.
如果你受不了，你就别看了
If you can't handle this, then look away.
好，杰米，我走！
Fine. Yeah, Jamie, I'll just leave!
-充电200 -不要，这会失败的！
- Charging 200. -Come on! This is wrong!
-你不是要离开吗？-你这是在某杀别人！
- Weren't you leaving? -You're murdering somebody!
是啊，我也许今晚就不该来
Yeah, I probably should've stayed in tonight.
-预备！
- Clear!
我的天
Oh, my God.
-她...她 -死了
- She's... She's... -Dead.
我想是
I think.
倒计时60秒
Counting off 60 seconds.
你看到任何大脑活动了吗？
Do you see any brain activity?
额
Um...
是有发生一些变化，但是我不确定是什么
I mean, something's going on, I'm not really sure what.
是在记录吗？
It's recording, isn't it?
是，是
Yeah. Yeah.
51，52，53...
Fifty-one, 52... Fifty-three...
54，55，56，57
Fifty-four, 55, 56, 57,
58，59
fifty-eight, 59,
-60秒到 -救她
-sixty seconds. -Get her out.
好，好，好
okay. okay. okay.
毯子在加热
Blanket's warming.
-她的体温需要在升高吗？-无所谓，快点
- What's her temp need to get to again? -Doesn't matter. Hurry up.
冷静点
Calm down.
-充电200 -等等！
- Charge 200. -Wait!
-预备！
- Clear!
不起作用
It's... It's not working.
当然不起作用
Of course it isn't.
显示屏上没心率是没用的
Paddles are useless without a heart rhythm.
你没有听她说吗？
Didn't you listen to her?
是啊，我还准备写下每一步...
Yeah, I was gonna write down all the steps...
快，闪开
Move! Just move.
闪开！
Move!
快过来帮忙！
地下室C层
紧急！！！
我们订了核磁共振成像在...嘿
Did we order an MRI on... Hey.
-等等，你在干什么？-我...
- Wait, what are you doing? -I...
不，她需要一支肾上腺素
No, she needs an epi.
哈？
Huh?
注射静脉的，你个白痴，天哪，那都准备好了
IV, you moron. God, it's already set up.
把药注射进去，该死
Just push the drug into the goddamn line!
冷静点，我能办到
Calm down! I got this.
上帝啊
God.
不管用啊，试试别的方法
It's not working. Try something else!
没有别的方法了
There is nothing else.
好吧，我...
Well, I...
这他妈怎么了？
What the fuck?
我们在做实验
It was an experiment.
他让我们把她的心脏弄停，但我们救不回来了
She had us stop her heart, and we can't get her back.
-她昏迷多久了？ -我也不清楚，几分钟
- How long has she been out? -I don't know, a couple of minutes.
我们应该试试除颤器
Look, I say we try the paddles.
不，别，把它放下！
No, no! Wait! Put them down.
停，停
I... Stop, stop.
你去换索菲亚，你在胸部按压
Take over for Sophia on the chest compressions.
到她的上方按压，力度在大些
Do them much harder, get on top of her if it helps.
索菲亚，把冷毯子给她盖上  她体温太高了
Sophia, put that cooling blanket on. She's too warm.
给除颤器充电到360，并准备好
Then charge the defib all the way to 360 and stand by.
只要我和杰米试到心跳
As soon as Jamie and I get you a heartbeat,
无论多微弱，你就把除颤器放到她胸口上
however fluttering, you put those paddles on her
然后给她电击
and give her full power.
毛毯，快
The blanket. Come on.
你在做心脏复苏是应该在给点肾上腺素
Got to push a lot more epi than what you've been doing.
不要停下，不要停，一直按压
Don't stop. Don't stop. Keep going.
好的
All right.
醒醒，考特尼
Come on, Courtney.
她缺氧了
She's hypoxia.
我们需要给她插氧气管
We need to intubate.
好吗？去！
All right? Go!
把这个拿掉
Let's get it off.
帮帮我
Help me.
面罩呼吸器
BVM.
好
All right.
快快快！
GO, go! go! 90'
预备！
Clear!
考特尼，能听见吗？
Courtney, can you hear me?
这太疯狂了，你知道吗？
You're crazy, you know that?
-你叫了雷来？-你能做好吗？
- You called Ray? -Were you getting it done?
有人能告诉我发生了什么吗？
Does somebody want to fill me in here?
恩，那发生的非常缓慢温和
Mmm, it happened very gently.
就像解脱了一样
Like, almost like an untethering.
然后我漂浮到了天花板上
And... And I... I floated to the ceiling.
我能看见自己的身体，能看见索菲亚和杰米
I could see my body. I could see Sophia and Jamie.
然后我能看到医院的屋顶
And then I could see the roof of the hospital.
我从来没去过那里
And I've never been up there.
怎么解释？
How do you explain that?
我解释不了
- I can't explain it.
你生气吗？
Are you mad at us?
我不知道我是什么心情
I don't know what to think
但我觉得你们都挺蠢的
other than you're all pretty stupid.
她能活过来很幸运
She's lucky to be alive.
她能活过来是靠的你
She's alive because of you.
还发生了什么？
What else happened?
你看到白光了吗？
Did you... Did you see a white light?
我不知道那是什么？那个...
I wouldn't call it that. It was...
更像是
It was more like...
纯能量体
Pure energy.
事实上，那东西看起来挺性感的
And honestly, it was kind of sexual, actually.
-是有点性感
-It was kind of sexual.
伙伴们，记录准备好了
Guys, playback's ready.
-嘿，看看这个
-Hey. Check this out.
好的，看我们从死亡的瞬间开始记录的
Okay, look. We're counting up from zero at the moment of death.
大脑的认知行为停止了
Cognitive activity has ceased.
你的心脏停止，没呼吸脉搏
Your heart stopped. No breathing, no pulse.
-15秒之后，那里开始变化
-We're 15 seconds in, and there.
看看那
Look at that.
你的前额叶像是有道闪电
Like a bolt of lightning in your prefrontal cortex.
我们也许正在目睹来世，朋友们
We might just be witnessing the afterlife, people.
有趣
Okay.
谁知道我们看见的是什么？
Who knows what we're looking at?
我们不是放射科医生
We're not radiologists.
也许那只是残余的电流
I mean, it could just be residual electricity.
-你懂得，神经停止工作 -好吧，我们看下一个
- You know, synapses shutting down. -Okay, we're moving on.
现在是死亡40秒之后
So, you've been dead almost 40 seconds now,
看发生了什么
and look.
这个区域也亮了起来，海马体
This area lights up, the hippocampus.
-这不是海马体 -当然是
- That's not the hippocampus. -Uh, of course it is.
这是腹侧被盖区
That is the ventral tegmental area.
那时大脑中最原始的区域
It's the oldest part of the brain,
管理着渴，饿，爱
governs thirst, hunger, love.
好吧，大医生们，很高兴你们这么愉快
Okay, doctors, I'm glad you're having fun.
我要先走了
Got to get out of here.
嘿 雷，别走
Hey, Ray, come on.
不用拦他，让他走吧
Hey, no. Just let him go.
再见了，朋友们
Adiés, adiés.
结束了，她的大脑正在死亡
It's over. Her brain's just dark now.
-不 - 没，看看那
- No. -Ah-ah. Look at that.
等一下，杏仁体有变化
Wait. Amygdala.
额，那是杏仁体，产生愤怒
Urn, that's the amygdala. Rage.
压力，情感，记忆的区域
Stress. Emotional memory.
无论你看到了什么
Whatever you were seeing,
这是我们把你就回来之前发生的
this is just before we pulled you out.
她还好吗？
Is she okay?
她在那坐了10分钟了
She's been sitting there for, like, 10 minutes.
-是吗？-是的
- Really? -Yeah.
你认为她在外面干什么？
What do you think she's doing out there?
我希望她不要试着去飞翔
I hope she doesn't try to fly.
如果有大脑化学物质被释放
If there were brain chemicals released,
影响可能还存留在她血液中
the aftereffects could still be in her bloodstream.
我有次服用了摇头丸
I took LSD once.
整整嗨了三天
I stayed awake for three days.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
我去看看她
I'm gonna go check on her.
我们走吧
Let's leave.
哦，哇哦
Ooh. Whoa.
这好高
That's high.
嘿
Hey
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我要去烤点买包
I'm gonna bake some bread.
面包怎么了？
What's with the bread?
考特尼昨晚烘焙了6条
Courtney baked it. Six loaves, last night.
她记起了她外婆的秘方
She remembered her grandmother's recipe.
她还跑了12英里
Also, she ran 12 miles.
-12英里？ -我们开始吧
- Twelve miles? - Let's begin.
我们正每隔十小时增大迈克尔·埃弗格林的药量
We've been ramping up Michael Evergreen with meds for ten hours,
而他的癫痫并没有好转
and his epilepsy hasn't gotten any better.
现在还发展出了皮疹
Now he's developed a skin rash.
很奇怪，药应该是起作用的
It's a mystery. The meds should be working.
卡马西平？
Carbamazepine?
什么？
What?
卡马西平有百分之11的几率会有不良反应
Carbamazepine has an 11% chance of reacting negatively
与拉莫三嗪，另一种药
with lamotrigine, which is the other drug
-迈克尔身上的 -是吗？
-that Michael's on. - Seriously?
说的没错，考特尼
Good catch, Courtney.
索菲亚，下一个病号
Sophia, next case.
额...阿黛尔·巩特尔 44岁 确认轻度精神混乱
Um... Adele Gunther. 44 years old. Admitted with mild confusion.
说她姐姐是假扮的，她不认识她
Says her sister's an impostor, she doesn't recognize her.
没有精神创伤历史 老年痴呆又太年轻了
No history of trauma. Too young for dementia.
我们要送她去精神科进行确诊
We're gonna send it out to Psychiatry for...
是卡氏综合症
It's Capgras syndrome.
-哈？-嗯？
- Huh? -Hmm?
-继续说 -卡氏综合症是
- Go on. - Capgras is an impairment
大脑面部认知中心损害
of the brain's facial recognition center.
一种非常罕见的疾病
And a very rare diagnosis.
V. S.拉马钱德兰 他的著作《脑的幻影》
V. S. Ramachandran, in his book, Phantoms of the Brain,
将前额皮质二分法与卡氏综合症联系起来
links frontal cortex dichotomies, like this, to Capgras.
这不是今年的课程
That's not on this year's syllabus.
这是我第一年的选修课
Optional reading in my first year.
恩，好，这样才像话
Hmm. Well, that's more like it.
我妹妹非常喜欢这段
My sister loved this piece.
卡马西平用药注意事项有20页那么长
Drug warnings for carbamazepine run 20 pages long.
她怎么能记住如此细节的东西？
How could she possibly recall a detail like that?
12年了，她怎么还能记住怎么弹钢琴？
How is she playing the piano again, after 12 years?
她弹的并不好听
She's not playing that well.
好像她的大脑被重置了
It's like her brain's been rewired,
接入了她曾经学过的所有东西
accessing everything she's ever learned.
我不关心她发生了什么
I don't care what happened to her.
这个实验必须现在终止
This experiment needs to end right now.
这种病态的迷恋并不值得你们去冒险
I'm not gonna risk everything for a morbid fascination you guys have.
你们认为你们是什么医学先驱者？
You think you're all medical pioneers?
你们只是一群有钱的孩子在这瞎闹
You're just a bunch of rich kids screwing around,
在你们成为富有的专家
before you become wealthy specialists
和拥有常青藤保险杠车贴的奔驰之前
with your Ivy League bumper stickers on your Mercedes.
我会一直在这陪着你的
I was with you until the end.
没人会在奔驰车上贴贴纸
No one puts bumper stickers on a Mercedes.
我想她弹得曲子并不是小把戏
I think we're way past parlor tricks here.
确实，我要做下一个
Uh, that does it. I'm going next.
- 好吧 -今晚，我去
- Okay. -Tonight. I am.
并且你们都要来
And you're all gonna be there.
今天真是个“去死”的好日子
It's a good day to die.
不！不！
No! No!
我的老天爷
Jesus Christ.
哇哦！
Whoo!
我死后就这个样吗？
Is that what I looked like?
是的，一模一样
Yep. Exactly like that.
-我就知道你会出现 -他去了多长时间了？
- I knew you'd show up.-How long has he been under?
啊，45秒
Uh, 45 seconds.
我记得你说过我们很愚蠢
I thought you'd had it with all this foolishness.
杰米要求我来这的
Jamie asked me to be here.
他想让我去救他
He wanted me to pull him out.
-胸部按压 - 1，2，3
-Pause compressions. -One, two, three...
-还是没心跳 -注射肾上腺素
- Still no heartbeat. -Pushing epi.
-醒醒，杰米 -他听不见你的
- Come on, Jamie, wake up. -He can't hear you.
索菲亚，准备插氧气管
Sophia, get ready to intubate.
哦，好的，额，我从来没这么做过
Oh, okay. Um, I've never done this before,
-等我一下 -做就行了
-so just give me a second... -Just do it!
雷，放松，没必要恐慌
Ray, relax. There's no need to panic.
让肾上腺素慢慢起效
Let's give the epi a second to work.
杰米...
Jamie...
- 准备
Clear!
-拿出来，快拿出来
-Take it out, take it out.
嘿...
Hey...
-天哪，杰米，杰米
-Jesus, Jamie, Jamie.
哇！我需要来杯酒
Whoo! I need a drink.
-喝喝喝！
- Shots, shots, shots!
耶 来吧!
Yeah, come on!
干杯！
Cheers!
-干杯!
-Salud!
你们要干嘛，要把墙拆了吗？
What do you guys think about taking this wall down?
-不不不 -我一直想要个阁楼
- No, no, no. -I've always wanted a loft.
- 哦，下冰雹了！考特尼！
-Oh! It's hailing! Courtney!
什么？
What?
-哦哦！-看我的！
- Oh! Oh! -I Watch it!
-噢 -这太疯了
- Oh! -This is crazy.
他们俩好像很合拍
It's like they're on the same wavelength.
我们应该把这个实验推广，像出售药品给俱乐部一样
We should bottle flatlining, sell it as a club drug.
-来，披上这个
-Here. Use this.
-嘿，不不！
-Hey, no, no!
-我的天哪
- Oh, my God.
这是我度过的最奇怪的夜晚之一
This has been the strangest night of my life.
你要做下一个吗，雷？
You going next, Ray?
-什么，重生实验？ -嗯哼
- What, flatlining?  -Uh-huh.
不可能
No way.
我会把你救回来的
I'd bring you back out.
也许会
Maybe.
你必须承认，我用除颤器用的很好
You have to admit, I was pretty good with that defibrillator.
还行吧
You were okay.
承认我和你一样是个好医生，能死吗？
Would it kill you to admit that I might be just as good a doctor as you?
我从来没说你不是
I never said you were not.
嘿，玛洛，你哥哥来了
Hey, Marlo, your brother's here.
你和我们一样没有社会经验
You have no more experience than the rest of us.
我有的
I do.
我曾在休斯顿当消防员
I was a firefighter in Houston.
接近6年的时间
Almost six years.
我要下一个去
I'm going next.
那非常有趣
It... It was super fun.
我感觉我非常有能量，整个城市的能量都在我这
I was all-powerful. I had the whole city to myself.
很奇怪不是吗？
It's weird, isn't it?
我以为那地方会有很多人，就像...
I thought there'd be more people, like...
不是应该看到...
Aren't you supposed to see...
所有去世的家人，或...
family members who've died, or...
也许那就没人，因为那就不属于我们
Maybe there's no one there because it wasn't really our time.
一切都很好吗？
Was it all fun?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我是说...有没有任何令人不安的事或...
I don't... I mean, like... Was there anything disturbing or...
没有
Not really.
为什么这么问？
Why?
没事
Nothing.
她稳定下来了
She's stabilizing.
我不明白，数据显示他开始
I don't understand. The data shows her starting
癫痫发作，然后症状就消失了
into a massive seizure, and then it just went away.
我给了她络艾塞半
I gave her Ativan.
谁允许的？
On whose authority?
对不起，下次我会申请的
I'm sorry. I'll get approval next time.
你救了她
You saved her life.
是的，我救了
Yes, I did.
我成耶稣了
I'm Jesus.
今天我碰到谁，我就能救他
Everyone I touch today, I'm gonna heal.
你懂得，这很有意思，因为你和考特尼都...
You know, it's funny, because you and Courtney both flat...
都做了重生实验
You both flatlined,
现在考特尼，注意力在过去
yet Courtney has focused on the past.
回忆，食谱
Memories, recipes.
而你注意力在现在，用你的直觉
Whereas you, you're... You're focused on the present, using your intuition.
你和考特尼有什么共同点吗？
What does that have in common with Courtney?
索菲亚，玛洛，你们需要去趟重症监护病房
Sophia, Marlo, you're needed in the ICU.
这是一种觉醒
It's an awakening.
过会见，耶稣
See you later, Jesus.
-觉醒？-是的
- An awakening? -Yeah.
你来这是做堕胎的吗？
You here for the abortion?
什么？
Huh?
欧内斯托 拉巴斯需要注射吗啡吗？
Should Ernesto La Paz get morphine?
-额
- Uh...
哦，我去看看病人
Oh. Uh, I'll, uh... I'll check with the resident.
-索菲亚？-恩？
-Sophia? -Hmm?
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
已经11点半了
It's 11:30 at night.
你没接到电话，也没什么安排
You're not on call, and you don't have anything scheduled.
不，我要去趟图书馆
No, I'm... I'm going to the library.
我要去做做功课
I'm just gonna do some more studying.
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
我要去泡个茶然后开始检查你
I'm making tea and we're gonna start reviewing
神经系统的专用名词的背诵
all of the terminology for the nervous system.
-但是我...-现在
- But I... -Now.
好吧
Okay.
索菲亚去哪了？
Where's Sophia?
我们要开始了，已经12点15了
We need to start. It's already 12:15.
这不会疼是吗？
This isn't gonna hurt, is it?
会注射麻醉剂的
The anesthesia will take care of that.
我要去三分钟
Three minutes.
但是，杰米只去了两分钟
Well, Jamie only did two.
我能说什么？
What can I say?
我比较好强
I'm competitive.
三分钟完成之后
After my three minutes are done,
这些是急救措施，按规定的顺序走
these are the interventions I want, in their specific order.
如果我没有立马醒来，我要你给我插管
If I don't come out right away, I want you to intubate me.
然后大量输送氧气，好吧？
Force the oxygen, okay?
嘿，我会把你救回来的
NHey, I'm gonna bring you out of it.
放松，享受这次旅程
Relax. Enjoy the experience.
好的，好的
Okay, okay.
输液开始
infusion's flowing.
她昏迷了，体温34度
She's out. Body temp's 94.
-充电200
- Charging 200.
-预备
- Clear.
心脏停搏
Asystole.
38岁男性，被水母蛰伤脸部
38-year-old male, stung in the face by a jellyfish.
水母
By a jellyfish.
好了，开始救她
That's it. Let's get her out.
肾上腺素注入
Epi in.
除颤器！充电200
Defib! Charge to 200.
准备
Clear.
-没脉搏 -该死，该做的都做了
- No pulse. -Damn it, we just had it.
再试一次
Juice her again.
我要注射肾上腺素和碳酸氢钠
I'm gonna push an epi and sodium bicarb.
除颤器，她现在不稳定
Defib. She's not stabilizing.
-充电300
- Charge 300
-预备，快醒醒
- Clear. Come on.
没心跳
No pulse.
这不起作用 我需要插管
This is not working. I need to intubate.
嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
冷静，交给我
Calm down. I got this.
360,预备
360. Clear.
快点醒来吧
Please.
她回来了
She's back.
-你还好吗？-没事的
-You good? -You're all right.
-恩 -坐好
-Yeah. -There you go.
我们安全的，没人会上来
We're safe. No one ever comes up here.
-那好美 -是吗？
-It's so beautiful. -Isn't it?
她的体温很低
Her temp's low.
脉搏还是很快
Pulse still racing.
我觉得三分钟太久了
Well, I think three minutes is too long.
哦，她这次不太顺利 难免的
Oh, look, she had a bad trip. It happens.
你现在又成专家了？
What, you're an expert?
是的，比你强
Uh, yeah, more than you.
-她还好么？-你去哪了？
- Is she okay? -Where have you been?
-玛洛没事 -恩，我还好
- Marlo is fine. -Yeah, I'll be okay.
我要下一个，现在就去
I'm going next. Right now.
-现在？-不行吗？
- Right now? -Why not?
清洁工还有20分钟就下去了
The cleaning crew is gonna be down there in like 20 minutes.
-好的 -不，我们太着迷这个了
- Okay. -No, we've gone too far.
不要再做重生实验了
No more flatlining.
好，你们三个增长了见识
Okay, so you three get to expand your consciousness
得到了学术优势，但我没有？
and get academic advantage, but I don't?
"优势"
Advantage.
你认为这会让你变得更好吗，索菲亚？
You think this makes you better, Sophia?
这可能会要你命
This makes you dead.
你见识比那多多了
You have much more sense than that.
雷，如果这困扰你了，你可以走开
Ray, if this bothers you so much, then just walk away.
-也许我应该 -你不会走的
- Well, maybe I should. -You're not going anywhere.
你和我们一样痴迷
You're in this as deep as the rest of us.
听着，我不关心这有多危险
Okay, look, I don't care how dangerous this is.
我比你们更需要这个
I need this more than any of you guys.
-雷，这是她的选择
-Ray, it's her decision.
就和我们一样
Just like it was each of ours.
如果索菲亚想要，那我们今晚就做
If Sophia wants to do this, then we're doing it tonight.
别待太久
Just don't stay in too long.
生物考试拿个B＋ 可不行
A B-plus on a biology exam is not acceptable.
不够
Not acceptable.
这样你是进不了前十的医学院校
That will not get you into a top-10 medical school.
有人从电梯下来了
Someone's coming down the elevator.
-什么？-赶紧救醒她
- What? -Get her out!
-快快快
-Come on, come on, come on.
开始 我们开始！
Let's go. Let's go!
注射1安培的肾上腺素
Pushing an amp of epi.
你要去干嘛？
Where the hell are you going?
开始按压胸部
Start compressions.
求求你了，老天，赶快救活她
Please, God, bring her back.
好想法，医生
Good thinking, Doctor.
我想这一定有用
I'm sure that's gonna help.
肾上腺素注入
Epi in.
停止按压
Pause compressions.
-预备
- Clear.
伊琳娜
Irina.
并不是只有你一个孩子想上好学校
You are not the only kid that is out there trying to get in.
该死
Shit.
一，二，三
One, two, three.
-心律失常 -充电360
V-tach. -Charging 360.
预备
Clear.
救过来了，她救过来了，我们走，快
We got her, we got her. Let's go, let's go. Come on.
我们会把你带出去的
We're gonna get you out of here.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
-来，你会好起来的 -快
- Come on, you'll be okay. Come here. -Come on.
-快！-好了，我抱住了
- Come on! -I got her, I got her.
-我的夹克 -知道了
- My jacket, my jacket. -Got it.
走，走
Go, go.
好，右拐
Okay. To the right.
开门，快进去
It's open. Just get in.
-好 -好，好
- Okay. -Okay，Okay.
你开车是吗？
Should you really be driving?
-等等 -哇，哇，哇哦！
- Wait! -Whoa, whoa, whoa!
噢，该死
Shit! Oh, shit!
你个混蛋！你丢下了我们
You asshole! You left us.
-你还好吗？-我他妈当然好了
- Are you okay? -The hell I did.
-我救了你们 -我们走！
- I saved your asses. -Let's go!
-他们来了！-稳住！
-Here they come! -Hold it right there!
我们离开这!
We got to get out of here!
坐稳了！
Hold on!
-哇！-我们开的太快了
- Whoa! -We're going too fast!
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
-该死 -有车！
- Shit! -Car!
-哦，天哪
- Oh, God!
哇，小心！
Oh, watch out!
哦，我的天
Oh, my God!
这一点也不好玩
It's not funny.
-哇哦！
-Whoa!
来了
Here we go.
哇哦！
Whoa!
-我们去哪？-哦！
- Where are we going? -Oh!
♪ So What, I'm a Wild child ♪
♪ Gunning for love ♪
♪ It's what makes the world go round ♪
噢耶
Hell yeah.
♪ Feel the walls come crashing down ♪
♪ Ain't no messiah ♪
♪ Where you at, girl? Where you, where you at? ♪
♪ Go home or go tough ♪
-喔
- Oh
♪ La, la, Ia, la, la, la, la, Ia ♪
♪ Bum, bum, lmma bang that drum ♪
♪ I blow up like bubble gum ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ They keep calling me a wild child ♪
♪ Oh, they all know that I'm... ♪
♪ When faced with the darkest day ♪
♪ With an endless night ♪
♪ When I lay awake ♪
♪ Only thought of you ♪
♪ Can pull me through ♪
♪ All I feel is you ♪
♪ How can it be that ♪
考特尼！
Courtney!
♪ But you've got to show me love ♪
♪ Give me a reason ♪
来
Come.
听着，我不知道是不是
Look, I don't know if it's the experience
重生实验对我的影响
of dying and coming back again,
但我现在感觉非常饥渴
but I have got a really intense craving right now.
对什么，冰激凌吗？
For what, gelato?
不
No.
哦，我的天，太爽了！
Oh, my God, this is crazy!
索菲亚
Sophia.
-索菲亚，打开门！
-Sophia, open this door!
我想门口可能有人
I... I, uh, I think there's someone at the door.
-索菲亚！-我不管
- Sophia! -I don't care.
-不要停
-Don't stop.
索菲亚，你给我开门
Sophia, I need you to open this door.
-索菲亚！
- Sophia!
很高兴认识你，曼宁太太
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Manning.
你怎么敢把外人带到我的公寓
How dare you bring someone back to my apartment.
我要搬出去
I'm moving out.
-你说什么？-我要自己找地方住
- What did you say? -I'm finding my own place.
你不能这么做
You will do no such thing.
你说什么都不管用了，老妈
See, it doesn't matter what you say, Mom.
不要吓唬我了，我已经25岁了
Whatever threats you make. I'm 25 years old.
成功或失败...
Succeed or fail...
我都要靠我自己了
I'm doing it on my own.
晚安
Good night.
-就这样
- All right.
晚安
Good night.
你怎么回家？
How are you getting home?
这边附近有个地铁站
There's a metro stop nearby.
听着，我有话对你说
Look, there's something I need to tell you.
额...
It's, um...
很重要
It's important.
你要说什么？
So, you gonna tell me or what?
我杀过一个人
I killed someone.
什么？
What?
两个月前
It was two months ago.
在我急诊室值班时
It was my ER rotation.
那个病人赛勒格杰恩
The patient's name was Cyrus Gudgeon.
他确诊被海蜇蜇伤
He was admitted for a jellyfish sting.
赛勒格杰恩，是的，我记着，他脸上被刺伤了
Cyrus Gudgeon. Yeah, I remember. He got stung in the face.
死于休克，对吗？
Died of shock, right?
不，他的死是因为我的失误
No, he died because of a mistake that I made.
我给他注射了肾上腺素和伤风药
I gave him epi and Benadryl.
但是这两种药物不能产生交叉反应
But those two drugs don't cross-react.
他体内有美托洛尔
He had metoprolol in his system.
他基本上是窒息而死的
He basically suffocated to death.
我上了36个小时的班
I... I'd been on duty for, like, 36 hours,
一定是我搞砸了忘记了问他
and I must have screwed up and forgotten to ask him
他是否服用其他药物
if he was taking any medications.
如果不是我的失误他现在肯定还活着
He would be alive right now if it wasn't for my mistake.
你为什么要告诉我这个？
Why are you telling me this?
因为我看见了他
Because I saw him.
赛勒斯，我在重生时看见了他
Cyrus. I saw him in my flatline.
这一定意味着什么，对吧？
And it must mean something, right?
嘿，错每个人都会犯
Hey, mistakes happen to everybody.
是，但是我每天努力工作
Yeah, but I work so hard every single day.
-我做的没错 -我知道
- I do the right thing. -I'm sure you do.
-我不是一个坏人 -是，你不是
- I'm not a bad person. -No, you're not.
我不是个坏人，我...
I'm not a bad person. I...
-一切都会好起来的，玛洛 -不，我很害怕
- Everything's gonna be fine, Marlo. -No, I'm scared.
我害怕
I'm scared.
等等，等下
Wait, wait, wait.
你...你不能...
You... You can't just...
我...对不起
I'm sor... I'm sorry.
对，我在做什么？
Yeah, what am I doing with you?
-我该走了，对不起 ，我不该... -不不不，等等
- I got to go right now. I'm sorry. No... -No. No, no, no, wait.
-恩，嗯哼
- Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
-该死，衣服扣还挺多 -这样...
- Damn, you have so many. -Just...
好了，好了
Okay, okay.
-我来，我来
- I got it, I got it.
- 考特尼！
- Courtney!
救命！
Help!
救命！特莎！
Help! Tessa!
特莎！
Tessa!
帮帮忙！
Help!
帮帮我妹妹！
My sister!
救命！
Help!
我妹妹！
My sister!
-我妹妹 -快上来
- My sister. -Come on.
不！我的妹妹！
No! My sister!
噢，特莎！不...特莎！
Oh, Tessa! My... Oh. Tessa!
不！
No!
我希望这之后咱两不会见面尴尬
I hope this doesn't become awkward.
现在说太晚了
Too late.
我不敢想象你想着我
I can't imagine what you must think of me.
为什么？
Why?
首先我告诉你那位病人的
Well, first I tell you that I'm responsible
死是我的责任
for the death of a patient,
然后我推开你又上了你
and then I go and totally attack you.
我认真的，为什么...
I mean, seriously, what...
你为什么会看上我？
What do you see in me?
你非常性感
You're really hot.
-讨厌
- Shut up.
-我该走了 -噢？
- l got to go. - Oh?
是的
Yeah.
是，是，是
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
那是第一年的第四个月
It was four months into our first year.
你在肿瘤病房做助手
You were assisting at the oncology ward.
一个乳腺癌的病人在做她第一次化疗
A breast cancer patient was there for her first round of chemo.
她非常焦虑和害怕，但是你坐在她旁边安抚她
She was anxious and scared, but you sat down and calmed her
询问她的孩子，她的工作来分散她的注意力
by asking about her kids, her job.
你太善良了
You were so kind.
你也没想到会有人在注视着你
You didn't think anyone was watching,
但是我在门口看了好久
but I was watching you through the door.
三小时之后，我驻足了一会
Three hours later, I stopped by,
又看到你在慰问她
and you were there checking on her again.
这就是我为什么喜欢你
That's what I see in you.
杰米？
Jamie?
考特尼？怎么了？
Courtney? What's going on?
我看到了我妹妹
I saw my sister.
什...什么？
Wh... What?
在岸边
At the waterfront.
是她
It was her.
我看到了我死去的妹妹
I saw my dead sister.
你...你在哪？
Where... Where are you?
我在家
I'm home.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't understand what's happening.
呆在那
Stay there.
我这就过去
I'm coming over.
我只是，想我妹妹了
I just... I miss my sister.
我应该告诉你们这一切
I should have told you all that
这不是关于
this wasn't about
科学发现
science or discovery.
我想我快要疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
我看到一些不存在的东西
Like I'm seeing things.
我曾做过的事
Something I did.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
对不起
I'm sorry.
♪ If you're happy ♪
♪ And you know it, clap your hands ♪
♪ If you're happy and you know it ♪
♪ Clap your hands ♪
♪ If you're happy ♪
♪ And you know it, tap your toe ♪
-特莎？
-Tessa?
♪ If you're happy and you know it ♪
♪ Then your face will surely show it ♪
特莎,真是你吗？
Tessa, is that really you?
♪ If you're happy and you know it, tap your toe ♪
♪ If you're happy ♪
♪ And you know it, clap your hands ♪
特莎，你还好吗？
Tessa, are you okay?
♪ If you're happy and you know it ♪
♪ Then your face will surely show it ♪
♪Clap your hands ♪
- 你是谁？- 考特尼！
- What are you? - Courtney!
考特尼
Courtney.
动起来！
Let's go!
嗨 四号病房怎么样了
Hi. An update on room four.
我们给了利尿灵药丸，但是尿量有限
We've given the Lasix bolus, and the output is limited.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
过去两小时不足50毫升
It's been less than 50 cc's in the last two hours.
好的
All right.
他们在防火梯下面发现了她
They found her at the bottom of a fire escape.
在尸检之后我们会明白死因
We'll know more after the autopsy,
但现在，我们不清楚她是摔下去的
but right now, it's unclear whether she fell,
还是跳下去的，谁也不知道
jumped, or God knows what.
- 我知道你们很喜欢她
- I know you all liked her.
对不起，但是现在，我需要你们
And I'm sorry, but for now, I need you
把她的病人分配到你们手中
to pick up her patient load and divide it amongst yourselves.
我们的医院还是要照常运作
We still have a hospital to run.
你们之中有知道她最近发生了什么吗？
Do any of you know what might have been going on with her?
有什么事瞒着我吗？
Is there something you're not telling me?
好吧
All right.
我不敢相信这是真的
It just doesn't feel real.
我知道
I know.
我不敢相信她离开了我们
You know, I can't believe she's gone.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
好的，一些奇怪的事发生在我们身上,我的大脑在捉弄我
Okay, something is happening to us, and my mind is playing tricks on me.
今天早上，我在游泳池里游泳
This morning, when I was swimming in the pool...
我不能说，好吗？
I can't talk, okay?
-我还要去查房 -伙伴们
- I have rounds right now. - Guys,
沃尔夫森好像已经知道我们有什么瞒着他了
Wolf son already knows we're holding something back.
学校会开始调查她的死因
The school is going to investigate her death.
我不相信这是自杀
I don't believe it was a suicide.
也许她摔倒了
Maybe she fell.
你在那
You were there.
发生了什么？
What happened?
额，她一直没开门
Uh, she never answered the door.
我以为...她睡觉了
I figured... She went to bed.
嘿，你们在讨论谁是杀手吗？
Hey, killer party, huh?
你们看起来糟糕极了
You all look like shit.
嘿，听着
Hey, listen,
如果学校发现我们在做重生实验
if the school finds out we have been flatlining,
我们会被开除的
we will be expelled.
然后你就可以和你的未来说再见了
And you can say goodbye to your future.
任何的记录找出来，毁掉它们
Any notes you've taken, destroy them.
我去考特尼的公寓，把她的手机，电脑
I'm gonna get into Courtney's apartment, get her phone, computer,
任何和实验有关联的
anything incriminating.
你知道吗，雷，你从一开始就是对的
You know, you were right this whole time, Ray.
我们应该听你的
We should've listened to you.
是的，说得对
Yeah, that's true.
这不管你的事，兄弟
This isn't on you, man.
你应该离我们远点
You should just walk away.
- 我们不会提到你的名字
- We'll keep your name out of it.
不
No.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
无论发生什么我们一起承担
Whatever happens to all of you happens to me.
-怎么了？-嘿
- Yes? - Hey.
坏消息
Look, bad news.
雷和我检查了她的公寓
Ray and I checked her apartment.
我们找到了她的电脑和一些笔记
We found her computer and some notes,
-但是没找到她的手机 -校园保安
-but not her phone. -Campus security
-可能在你们之前去了 -知道了
-could have gotten there before you. -Okay.
假设你是对的并且不是犯罪调查
Assuming you're right and it's not a criminal investigation,
她的东西都在她自己身上
then all that stuff stays with her body.
这样你就可以去下面找找
Meaning you can go down there and look for it.
下面哪？
Go down where?
还能是哪？该死的停尸间
Where do you think? The goddamn morgue.
好的
Okay.
姓名
霍姆斯，考特尼
尸体编号
109204-12
凶   手
玛洛
Marlo.
-玛洛?
- Marlo?
赛勒斯
Cyrus.
- 杰米...
- Jamie...
-杰米
Jamie.
我看到一些不存在的东西
Like I'm seeing things.
我曾做过的事
Something I did.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
对不起
I'm sorry.
特莎？
Tessa?
特莎，真的是你吗？
Tessa, is that really you?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你是谁？
What are you?
我的天
Jesus Christ.
那是什么？
What was that?
她在和某人谈话
She was talking to someone.
有人在那
Someone was there.
你也不能确定
You don't know that.
她可能产生了幻觉
She could've been hallucinating.
在我看来并不是
It didn't sound like that to me.
如果那真的是特莎呢？
What if it was Tessa?
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
她看见了某个东西 你也听到了
She saw something. You heard her.
她说她曾做过什么事
She said that she did something.
是她的错
Something was her fault.
如果那是？如果...
What if that's it? What if...
如果是我们的罪恶找上我们怎么办？
What if our sins are coming for us?
罪恶 那太扯了
Sins. That's ridiculous.
那我们该怎么做？
So, what are we gonna do?
我们要怎么做？
What are we gonna do?
我们要告诉彼此自己的秘密
We're gonna tell each other the goddamn truth.
那是我们应该做的
That's what we're gonna do.
额...
Uh...
我曾认识...一个女孩
There's a girl I... I used to know.
艾丽西娅
Alicia.
她是个服务员在我爸的乡村俱乐部工作
She was a waitress at my dad's country club.
我的天
Oh, my God.
-你杀了她？-什么，不是
- You killed her? -What? No.
不，我没杀任何人
No, I did not kill anyone.
我...
I, uh...
我... 我...
I... I...
我让她怀孕了
I got her pregnant.
我想帮她，你知道吗？
I wanted to help, you know?
支付堕胎的费用，做... 陪她做手术
Pay for the abortion, be... Go with her for the procedure.
无论如何，那天来了
Anyway, uh, the... The day came,
我... 我没有做到
and I... I couldn't deal with it.
我...我开车走了
I... I drove right past.
我丢下了她让她自己谋生
I left her to fend for herself.
她在你重生时出现了？
And she showed up in your flatline?
我希望只是如此
I wish that was all.
她昨晚又出现了
She showed up last night, too.
所以你是被鬼缠身了？
So you're being haunted by somebody that's alive.
-你在胡说什么？-这个
- What are you talking about? -This.
这是我想说的
I am talking about this.
艾丽西亚攻击了我
Alicia did this to me.
除非不是她
Only it wasn't her.
就像不是考特尼的妹妹一样
Just like it wasn't Courtney's sister.
那是什么？
Then what was it?
杰米，是什么？
Jamie, what?
我...我不知道
I... I don't know.
那些东西以我们的良心为食
Something feeding off our guilty conscience.
你什么意思？像...
What do you mean? Like...
某种魔鬼？
Something demonic?
-也许是我们的过去，罪恶
-Maybe it's using our pasts, our sins.
等等，等等
Wait, wait.
我们都是相信科学的人
We're rational people here.
你们不能打自己的脸
You could have stabbed yourself.
人们经常服用药物伤害自己
People on drugs hurt themselves all the time.
这一定有合理的解释
There has to be a logical explanation.
我17岁时
I was 17.
她名字叫伊琳娜·王，她各科平均分都比我高
Her name was Irina Wong, and she had a higher GPA than I did,
我黑进了她的短信
so I hacked her text messages
我把她的裸照发给了全班同学
and I sent her naked photos to the whole class.
那毁了她
It destroyed her.
这些忏悔有什么意义？
What is the point in confessing all of this?
这只是你们的大脑在作怪
This is clearly just happening here.
-那个东西... -听着，考特尼对我说过
- That thing... -Look, look, Courtney said to me
她认为我们可能打开了另一个空间的门
she thinks maybe we opened a door.
等等，你之前就知道？
Wait, so you knew?
你们知道重生时会有不好的事发生？
You and Courtney knew there was a downside to flatlining,
然后...你还让我和玛洛继续实验？
and... And you still let me and Marlo go in?
嘿，听着，我以为这是必须要经历的体验
Hey, look, I thought it was just part of the experience.
就像副作用一样
Side effects may include
口干，幻觉，死亡的恐惧
dry mouth, hallucinations, existential dread.
我不知道这个副作用会出现
I did not know that the side effects would show up
并追杀我们
and start hunting us down.
发生在我们身上的一切一定有科学的解释
There is a scientific explanation to all of this.
这已经没法用科学解释了
We're way beyond explanations.
好的
Okay.
如果考特尼是对的
If Courtney was right,
我们身上不管发生了什么
whatever's happening to us,
这些幻觉，幽灵，不管是什么
these hallucinations, these hauntings, whatever it is,
它只会变得更糟
it's only gonna get worse.
直到我们想出
Until we figure it out,
在我们想出办法之前
until we figure out what to do,
杀死她的东西也会杀死我们
whatever killed her is gonna kill all of us, too.
看到这种肿块病变会引发脑软化
Note the negative mass effect secondary to the encephalomalacia.
在幕上的白色物质是多发病灶
There are multiple foci of high T2 and FLAIR signal intensity
T2信号和FLAIR序列呈明显高信号
in the supratentorial white matter.
T2  核磁T2加权像适合观察组织病变
FLAIR  磁共振成像液体衰减反转恢复序列
这些发现是不特定的，但是大多数符合
These findings are nonspecific, but most in keeping with
慢性微血管的病变
chronic microangiopathic changes.
你会发现没有脑积水
You'll note there's no hydrocephalus.
这没有形成脑疝 这些血管清晰可见
There's no brain herniation. The vessels are well seen.
你看到这些灰色物质
You'll note that the gray matter
完全维持分化
differentiation is completely maintained.
你这个婊子 我不敢相信你竟然和他睡了
You little slut. I can't believe you slept with him.
你不仅是个不可救药的书呆子
Not only are you a hopeless grind,
还是个不成熟，爱发牢骚，爱哭的贱人
but you're an immature, whiney, crybaby bitch.
- 够了，停下！-你说什么？
- Okay, stop! -Excuse me?
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
不
No.
不不不！
No!No!No!
开门！
No!
不
No.
停下来！
Stop!
停下来！不！
Stop! No!
不！
No!
停下！不！
Stop! No!
嘿
Hey.
Hey
你来这干什么？
What are you doing here?
你最近还能看见赛勒格杰恩吗？
Have you seen Cyrus Gudgeon lately?
如果你是在开玩笑
If that's supposed to be a joke,
-这一点也不好笑 -不是玩笑
-it's not funny. -it's not a joke.
那你想说什么？
Then what?
我去看了尸检报告
I pulled the autopsy report.
上面没写有美托洛尔
It says nothing about metoprolol.
所以我又去找了原版实验室的血液报告
So then I went back to the original path lab notes of the blood test,
那里确实有
and there it was.
美托洛尔
Metoprolol.
我要进门了
I'm going inside.
为什么尸检报告和原版记录的不一样，玛洛？
Why wouldn't the autopsy report match with the notes, Marlo?
玛洛？
Marlo？
玛洛
Marlo.
你更改了尸检报告吗？
Did you change that autopsy report?
我必须保护自己
I had to protect myself.
保护你自己？真的吗？
Protect yourself? Really?
通过让他看起来死于蛰伤
By making it look like he died from a sting
而不是你用药失误？
and not a drug you administered?
我懂
I know.
-我知道 这不对 -你必须说出真相
- I know. It was wrong of me. -You got to tell someone.
-我说了 我告诉你了-院长，玛洛
- I am. I'm telling you. -The dean, Marlo.
你必须告诉院长你更改了报告
You have to tell the dean you changed that report.
为什么？
Why?
-现在说有什么好处？-你是认真的吗？
- What good is that gonna do now?  -Really?
你还不明白吗？
You don't see it?
重生实验 赛勒格杰恩
It's your flatline, Cyrus Gudgeon.
你知道吗，我真的很喜欢和你相处
You know, it was so nice being with you
经过这么长时间 意识到 你是真的喜欢我
and realizing, after all this time, that you actually like me.
但现在你又想毁了我们的感情
And now you have to go and spoil it.
-我来是因为我喜欢你 -恩，说的挺容易
- I am here because I like you. -Yeah, well, it's easy for you.
你根本没做出任何牺牲
You don't have to sacrifice anything.
我即将拿到学位成为顶尖医学院的医生
I'm becoming a doctor with a degree from a top medical school.
我努力一生就为了这个
I've worked my whole life for this.
但现在...我犯了个错 是的，我承认
And now, I... I made one mistake. I mean, admitting it
这样也救不了那个人
is not gonna bring the guy back.
只能毁了我的职业生涯
All it's gonna do is end my career.
这就是你关心的
That is the point here,
你的职业生涯
your career.
如果你执意更改尸检报告 那...
If you were willing to change an autopsy report, then...
你说啊
Say it.
那你不应该成为医生
Then maybe you shouldn't be a doctor.
嘿 额，是贝弗莉·王吗？
Hi. Um, is this Beverly Wong?
你是住在东哈德利镇的贝弗莉·王？
Beverly Wong from East Hadley?
是吗？
It is?
你有个女儿叫伊琳娜吗？
Do you have a daughter named Irina?
嘿
Hey.
谢谢你陪我一起
Thanks for coming with me.
你还能租个再小点的车吗？
Could you have rented a smaller car?
你确定这是同一个伊琳娜？
You're sure it's the same Irina?
额...
Uh...
伊琳娜
Irina.
是我
Yes.
我是索菲亚
It's Sophia.
在东哈德利镇
From East Hadley.
我们上的同一所学校
We went to the same high school.
对不起，我知道，那是...好久的事了
I'm sorry. I know, it... It's... It's been forever.
我，额...
I, um...
我真的需要和你好好谈谈，能坐下说嘛...
I really needed to talk to you, so I was hoping we could sit down...
为了什么？
What is this about?
你从不知道这件事，但是...
You never knew this, but...
是我把你的照片发给全班同学的
I was the one who sent your pictures to the whole class.
是我干的
That was me.
我再也不能容忍我自己了
I can't stand myself to think about it.
说到底，这是个非常恶劣的事 我知道
Bottom line, it was an awful thing to do. I know that.
你想怎么样？
What do you want?
我希望你能接受我的道歉
I'd like you to accept my apology.
没必要
It's not necessary.
好吗？我已经看开了
Okay? I've moved on.
伊琳娜...这很重要，好吗？
Irina... This is important, okay?
我非常对不起你
I am so sorry.
伊琳娜，求求你原谅我吧
Irina, please.
索菲亚
Sophia.
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她怎么说？
What'd she say?
嘿，玛洛，我是杰米
Hey, Marlo, it's Jamie.
- 嘿 - 听着，我们虽然有点随意
- Hey. - Look, we're just kind of riffing here,
但是也许你找到你犯过的错
but maybe you find whoever you've wronged,
或你感觉内疚的事
whatever you're feeling guilty about,
并负起责任
and you take responsibility.
试试吧，万一有效果呢？
I mean, look, who knows if it'll work?
但我们也不损失什么，对吧？
But what have we got to lose?
艾丽西亚！
Alicia!
艾丽西亚
Alicia.
嘿，是...我
Hey. It's... It's me.
我是杰米
It's Jamie.
你在这干什么，杰米？
What are you doing here, Jamie?
这是你儿子？
He's your son?
嘿 嘿...我是来道歉的
Hey. Hey... I came to apologize.
我不应该抛弃你
For taking off on you.
我...我慌了 我是个懦夫
I... I panicked. I was a coward.
我应该陪着你的
I should have been there for you.
但是你没有
But you weren't.
听，我...
Look, I...
我想弥补我的过错
I want to make amends.
做正确的事
Do what's right.
帮...帮助你
Help... Help you out.
无论你需要什么
Whatever you need.
艾丽西亚
Alicia.
这个男人是谁，妈妈？
Who is that man, Mommy?
真的有来世吗？
什么？
What?
你他妈在干嘛？
What the hell?
我必须要停下来 对不起
索菲亚？
Sophia?
我刚收到一条玛洛的信息
I just got a message from Marlo.
有什么事不对劲，她手机也关机了
Something's wrong. And her phone is off.
我们要找到她
We need to find her.
好的，你在哪？
Okay. Uh, where are you?
我...我去找你
I'm... I'm gonna come to you.
玛洛？
Marlo？
玛洛！
Marlo!
她不在这
She's not here, man.
等等，等等！
Wait. Wait!
玛洛？
Marlo？
不用找了，她在这
Forget it. She's here.
最快速度过来找我！
Come as fast as you can!
我就在附近
I'm nearly there.
你快点
You got to hurry.
雷！
Ray!
她肯定在下面 快
She must be down there. Come.
好的
Okay.
啊，快点！
Oh, come on!
-不，我的天 -不不不不！
- Oh, my God. -No, no, no, no, no!
不，我的天 她去了多久了
Oh, my God. How long has she been under?
已经去了4分钟了
It's been over four minutes.
-面罩呼吸器？-好的
- BVM? -Sure.
快点，我们需要给她氧气！
Come on. We need oxygen!
赛勒 对不起
Cyrus. I'm so sorry.
原谅我吧
Forgive me.
你能原谅我吗？
Will you please forgive me?
没脉搏
No pulse.
过来按压胸部
Take over the compressions.
快快快！
Go, go, go!
啊！
Ahhh!
不管用，该死
It's not working. Shit.
停
Stop.
没反应
Nothing.
雷
Ray.
玛洛，你不明白吗？
Marlo, don't you get it?
我需要你回来
I need you to come back.
为了我
To me.
玛洛，玛洛...
Marlo, Marlo...
玛洛？玛洛...
Marlo? Marlo.
不！不！
No! No!
玛洛
Marlo.
你必须原谅你自己
You have to forgive yourself.
原谅自己，玛洛
Forgive yourself, Marlo.
不！
No!
充电360
Charge 360.
雷？
Ray?
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
噢，我的...
Oh, my...
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
嘿
Hey
来
Here.
-坐好
-There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗？
You okay?
恩
Yeah.
我找到那个女孩了
I found the girl.
还有那个小男孩
And, uh, a little boy.
是的
Yeah.
不去他妈的洛杉矶了
The hell with going to L.A.
我要在这当实习医生
I'm getting a residency right here.
靠他们近点
Be near them.
我要努力尝试了
I'm gonna try.
考特尼是对的
Courtney was right.
光道歉是不够的
It's not enough to apologize.
我们必须要面对自己所做的事
We have to face up to what we've done,
然后原谅自己
and then forgive ourselves.
有些底线是不能跨越的
Some lines should not be crossed.
我们失去了一个朋友
We lost a friend.
我们将永远不会同过去一样
We will never be the same.
你现在在哪？
Where were you?
我和院长说了
I talked to the dean.
怎么样？
How'd it go?
我在观察期
I'm on probation.
你带来了吗？
Did you bring it?
来
Here.
现在只有考特尼知道了
Only Courtney knows now.
没有考特尼在这感觉好奇怪
Feels so weird just being here without Courtney.
有人想说点什么吗？
Anyone want to say something?
我们喝个烂醉吧
Let's just get hammered.
你来说点什么吧
Why don't you say something?
敬考特尼
To Courtney.
♪ You flipped the page And slipped away ♪
♪ Never thought that you were ♪
♪ Someone to say things that you didn't mean ♪
♪ You didn't even call to wish me sweet dreams ♪
♪ I really thought we made a sweet team ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ But don't cry ♪
♪ Consider this a lullaby ♪
♪ Sweet dreams... ♪
♪ Ticking clocks on the wall ♪
♪ Waiting for your call ♪
♪ Mmm, but that cuckoo bird ♪
♪ Won't sing at all ♪
♪ Never thought that you would ♪
♪ Take everything we had and loved and leave ♪
♪ You didn't even call to wish me sweet dreams ♪
♪ I really thought we made a sweet team ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ But don't cry ♪
♪ Can't you see that you're a love of mine? ♪
♪ Sweet dreams ♪
♪ Always thought you were the sweetest thing ♪
♪ Uh-huh... ♪
♪ But don't cry ♪
♪ Consider this a lullaby ♪
♪ In sweet dreams ♪
♪ Sweet dreams ♪
♪ Oh, sweet dreams ♪